{
    "subject": "resource/Murder,_My_Sweet",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Adrian_Scott",
    "human_readable": "The producer of Murder, My Sweet is Adrian Scott.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8688818216323853,
            "question": "Who was involved in producing Murder, My Sweet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8273338675498962,
            "question": "What is the name of the producer of Murder, My Sweet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8135387301445007,
            "question": "Who produced the movie Murder, My Sweet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7891201972961426,
            "question": "Is Adrian Scott a director or a producer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7533199191093445,
            "question": "Adrian Scott is known for producing which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.685946524143219,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Adrian Scott."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.625737726688385,
            "question": "What is the profession of Adrian Scott?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6168813705444336,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of a film produced by Adrian Scott?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5644246935844421,
            "question": "Adrian Scott worked in which industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4667746126651764,
            "question": "What movie was directed by Edward Dmytryk and produced by Adrian Scott?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of Murder, My Sweet is Adrian Scott.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6843_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adrian Scott worked in which industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6843_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the name of a film produced by Adrian Scott?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6843_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the profession of Adrian Scott?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6843_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6843_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. In particular, document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6843/re-ranker-msmarco/22.txt states that Adrian Scott was a screenwriter and motion picture producer with MGM and RKO from 1930-1947, and another document mentions that he produced the film \"Murder, My Sweet\" (1944) based on the novel by Raymond Chandler."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states under the entry for \"Murder, My Sweet (1944)\" that \"PRODUCER: Adrian Scott\", which directly supports the statement that Adrian Scott was the producer of Murder, My Sweet."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}